{
    "id": "2e083437763f4c398f91b2cf036a86b5",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Keep",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I was taken .............................. by her impertinence.",
            "description": "When you are taken aback, you are shocked.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "aback",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afe1a1c359b34f1d96ca409cde8c8e74"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child does not take ............................ either of his parents.",
            "description": "To take after somebody is to resemble them in looks or behavior.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dc161d650cbc4a6abd755e4310532dfd"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you have ten candies and take ............................... six, you are left with four.",
            "description": "To take something away is to remove it or subtract it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7a4dbaae9f564d0eb897b839035d4102"
        },
        {
            "question": "The fact that the athlete had used performance enhancing drugs, took .............................. his achievements.",
            "description": "To take away from something is to make it seem less valuable.",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "from",
                "away from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fb02766ecc1f43eda16211547f84cb8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took the shelves ................................... to clean them properly.",
            "description": "To take something apart is to disassemble them.",
            "answers": [
                "apart",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "228d987f56774e8492abd54a1ee7e51f"
        },
        {
            "question": "A public outcry forced the minister to take ................................ his offensive comments.",
            "description": "To take something back is to say that you didn't really mean what you had said.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e578d3ff08344b76a6432233ee936a5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please take .................................... my address and phone number.",
            "description": "Take down can mean write down. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8c2cb9f9395f4e5b91ede3e299b5907f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don't take him ............................. an idiot.",
            "description": "\r\nTo take somebody for an idiot is to regard them as an idiot.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4fb54916e2d24e6b87f2a9d52232ee6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took .............................. a pup last month and now he is my best buddy.",
            "description": "To take in somebody is to give them shelter.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3508ff84d24e44dc89f2dbe7bdcc40a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I took .............................. every word they uttered. It was such a mesmerizing performance.",
            "description": "To take in something is to absorb it or understand it.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7f1088c6c31459eb654c768df9cac9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although the airplane took .................................... 30 minutes late, it arrived on time.",
            "description": "When an airplane takes off, it begins to fly.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f93d2bad458b4103a492bdd66c5510c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am too busy to take .............................. any extra work.",
            "description": "To take on a job is to accept it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d8c8f4fbdf69499d848a5eede8e212de"
        }
    ]
}